Campus Construction; Collection ua950.005
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Campus Construction Progress Reports Walter Tisdale #1-237, 1963-1974 (Box 1, Folder 13, 37)
  - Campus Progress Report No. 201, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 September 6
  - Campus Progress Report No. 202, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 September 13
  - Campus Progress Report No. 203, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 September 14
  - Campus Progress Report No. 204, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 September 27
  - Campus Progress Report No. 205 (a), Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 October 4
  - Campus Progress Report No. 205 (b), Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 September 27
  - Campus Progress Report No. 206, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 October 19
  - Campus Progress Report No. 207, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 November 21
  - Campus Progress Report No. 208, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1972 December 15
  - Campus Progress Report No. 209, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 January 9
  - Campus Progress Report No. 210, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 January 17
  - Campus Progress Report No. 211, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 February 1
  - Campus Progress Report No. 212, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 February 2
  - Campus Progress Report No. 213, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 February 6
  - Campus Progress Report No. 214, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 March 15
  - Campus Progress Report No. 215, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 April 2
  - Campus Progress Report No. 216, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 April 26
  - Campus Progress Report No. 217, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 May 2
  - Campus Progress Report No. 218, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 May 17
  - Campus Progress Report No. 219, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 May 31
  - Campus Progress Report No. 220, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 June 7
  - Campus Progress Report No. 221, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 June 12
  - Campus Progress Report No. 222, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 July 11
  - Campus Progress Report No. 223, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 July 17
  - Campus Progress Report No. 224, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 July 18
  - Campus Progress Report No. 225, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 August 31
  - Campus Progress Report No. 226, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 September 10
  - Campus Progress Report No. 227, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 October 2
  - Campus Progress Report No. 228, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 October 16
  - Campus Progress Report No. 229, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 October 24
  - Campus Progress Report No. 230, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 October 29
  - Campus Progress Report No. 231, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 November 2
  - Campus Progress Report No. 232, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 November 7
  - Campus Progress Report No. 233, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1973 November 9
  - Campus Progress Report No. 234 (a), Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1974 February 5
  - Campus Progress Report No. 234 (b), Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1974 July 24
  - Campus Progress Report No. 235, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1974 February 27
  - Campus Progress Report No. 236, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1974 May 6
  - Campus Progress Report No. 237, Letter from Walter M. Tisdale to Vice President John W. Hartley, 1974 May 15
- Construction News Clippings, 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- State University of New York at Albany, Data Booklet, 1963 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- State University of New York Master Plan Revised 1964 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Atlas Cement Promotional Brochures; SUNY Master Plan; SUNY Summary Bulletin, 1964-1965; 1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- State University of New York Summary Bulletin Fall 1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Dormitory Authority of the State of New York Annual Report, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Budget Proposals 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- SUNY Planning Guidelines for Facilities at University Centers prepared by William T. Conway, Program Coordinators for University Centers, 1965 February (Box 1, Folder 21)
- SUNYA: Comprehensive Campus Plan Report Action Program, 1965 May 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- New Campus, Miscellaneous, Memos, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Ezra Stoller Associates [photographs], [State University of New York at Albany Camps 1967 ] (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
- Building Progress Report, 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Documents and News Clippings, 1967-1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- 1974 Comprehensive Campus Plan Updating SUNYA, 1967 June 7 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- State University of New York at Albany, Justification for Social Science Building II, 1967 August (Box 1, Folder 27)
- State University of New York at Albany, Justification for Business Building II, 1967 August (Box 1, Folder 28)
- 1974 Comprehensive Campus Plan Updating SUNYA, 1967 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Times Union Newspaper Oriental Magnificence of Persian Medieval Form Seems Modern, 1967 November 12 (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- 1974 Comprehensive Campus Plan Updating SUNYA (1 of 2), 1968 July (Box 1, Folder 31)
- 1974 Comprehensive Campus Plan Updating SUNYA (2 of 2), 1968 July (Box 1, Folder 32)
- 1974 Comprehensive Site Plan Updating SUNYA, Summary Report, 1968 July (Box 1, Folder 33)
- 1974 Comprehensive Site Plan Updating State University of New York at Albany July 1968 Edward Durell Stone & Associates Architect [1 of 2], 1968 July (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Summary Report 1974 Comprehensive Site Plan Updating State University of New York at Albany July 1968 Edward Durell Stone & Associates Architect, 1968 July (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Committee of the University, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Edward Durell & Associates, Edward Durell Stone (New: Archstone 1971 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Lounge Space, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- State University of New York at Albany, Program for New Academic Building, (Annex A), 1972-1978 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Program for New Academic Building (Annex "A") President Benezet 1972 February 2 [1 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Program for New Academic Building (Annex "A") President Benezet 1972 February 2 [2 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Program for New Academic Building (Annex "A") President Benezet 1972 February 2 [3 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Campus Environmental Improvement Program, SUNY College of Environmental Science and Forestry, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Campus Environmental Improvement Program, SUNY College of Environmental Science and Forestry, Copy, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Stone and SUNYA Campus Exhibit Cards, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- New Campus Rooms and Offices binder, moving plan, 1965-1966 (Box 1)
- Goals and Objectives Workpaper: University at Albany Master Plan: State University of New York: State University Construction Fund: Hiller July 1997, 1997 July (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
- UAlbany Expansion, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- University at Albany State University of New York Campus Heritage Preservation Plan January 2009 [1 of 3], 2009 January (Box 2, Folder 2)
- University at Albany State University of New York Campus Heritage Preservation Plan January 2009 [2 of 3], 2009 January (Box 2, Folder 3)
- University at Albany State University of New York Campus Heritage Preservation Plan January 2009 [3 of 3], 2009 January (Box 2, Folder 4)
- University at Albany State University of New York Campus Heritage Preservation Plan January 2009 [3 of 3], 2009 January (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Draft Scoping Document for Environmental Impact February 12, 2009, 2009 February 12 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- "Futures: State University of New York and your Children," Pamphlet, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
- State University of New York at Albany, Justification for Humanities Building II, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Edward Durell Stone. Recent & Future Architecture (Published book Horizon New York Press, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
- Uptown Campus, 30-40,000 Student Scenario, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Campus Plans for State University of New York, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
- Campus Plans for State University of New York, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 6)